

VINCENT OKEKE

Project Management | Marketing | Business

PROFILE

I am a highly tech savvy professional who has worked in a number of local and international organisations. My core skills include business and marketing strategy/consultancy, and project management. I possess a total of 10 years post-graduate professional work experience.

CONTACT

Phone: +234 806663 1119

Email: okekevincent@gmail.com

Add.: 5 Afusat Kekere Ekun,

Addo, Ajah, Lagos

Web.: www.vincentokeke.com

BIODATA

Country of Origin: Nigeria

Date of Birth: 30/12/1988

Gender: Male

Marital Status: Married

EDUCATION

Master in Human Resource and Industrial Relations (MHRIR) Lagos State University, Ojo | 2014 - 2016

Bachelor of Art, Mass Communications
Anambra State University, Uli | 2005 – 2009

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS

- Institute of Strategic Management (ISMN): Associate Member (2013)
- Nigerian Institute of Management, (NIM): Graduate Member (2011)
- Advertising Practitioners Council of Nigeria: Associate Member (2014)

EXPERIENCE

Dovichi Worldwide Technology Company Limited

Lead Strategist | 2015 - Date

To oversee the overall business operations, and implement growth strategy for company's digital products. Lead and motivate team members and drive their productivity towards the company's goals.

Unicaf

Country Consultant (Nigeria) | 2018 – Date Digital Marketing Consultant | 2015 - 2018

Provide strategy for effective growth-hacking and special project execution. Some of the project areas i worked on include Digital Marketing (Strategy, planning and executive), Strategic partnership implementation.

e-Scape Technologies Limited

Marketing & Business Strategist (VAS) | 2013 - 2015

Digital marketing, and business development with OEM and ODM partners. Enhancing strategic partnerships for product growth, market research.

REFERENCES

Oleka Bright gentlebright007@gmail.com 234 8068319302 Product Director | Judy Legal Michael Ohadugha mikelozytex@yahoo.com 234 8062895692 Founder | Soft.ng